<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="sentences">
        <item>You are beautiful !</item>
        <item>Today is a great day !</item>
        <item>I love you but it\'s more important to love yourself</item>
        <item>Look around you for something beautiful. Beauty is everywhere !</item>
        <item>Today is a beautiful day! </item>
        <item>Smile is always inspirational :) </item>
        <item>The sun still exists beyond the clouds </item>
        <item>every cloud has a silver lining</item>
        <item>Time is a precious friend, take care of it </item>
        <item>Every day everything is different: from the growing tree leaf to the fading rose petal </item>
        <item>1,2,3 ... Smile </item>
        <item>Think back to your last holiday trip</item>
        <item>Life is good </item>
        <item>Think about your favorite fragrance</item>
        <item>All you need is love !</item>
        <item>At night there are over a billion stars that shine just for you </item>
        <item>A simple smile makes life so good! </item>
        <item>Every moment is precious, breathe and smile! </item>
        <item>It\'s inner beauty that matters, take care of yourself! </item>
        <item>Nothing better than enjoying life every moment </item>
        <item>Recite out loud 3 things that you like about yourself </item>
        <item>Recite out loud 3 things that you enjoy in life </item>
        <item>Charity begins at home: treat yourself! </item>
        <item>You are the smartest person in the world </item>
        <item>Giving Makes You Happy: Try to give lots of compliments to others today </item>
        <item>Think back to the last sunset you saw </item>
        <item>Think back to the last sunrise you saw </item>
        <item>Take some time to look around you: we often no longer notice the beauty that surrounds us </item>
        <item>Who is beautiful, smart and kind? You! </item>
        <item>Trust yourself! </item>
        <item>Life is short, today dares to do something new :) </item>
        <item>Hatred weighs heavily, so love everyone to have a light heart! </item>
        <item>No stress! Life is too short! </item>
        <item>Close your eyes and think of the sound of the waves and the smell of the sea </item>
        <item>Close your eyes and think of the sound of the wind in the trees and the smell of freshly cut grass </item>
        <item>Do you want a picnic? no need to leave your home: a tablecloth on the ground, a bouquet of flowers, a baguette and ham! It\'s easy to have fun </item>
        <item>A desire to travel? no need to leave your home: put on your swimsuit, a glass of margharita, tropical music! It\'s easy to have fun </item>
        <item>Remember to give yourself a little pleasure! A square of chocolate? A massage session? A good book to read? </item>
        <item>Take a minute to relax and unwind </item>
        <item>Hello! Take care about you </item>
        <item>Think of a good action and realize it! </item>
        <item>Close your eyes and imagine yourself at the top of a mountain with a breathtaking view of nature! What a beautiful planet we live in </item>
        <item>Think of a good memory and count 10 to 0 in your head very slowly: it feels good </item>
        <item>Think back to your good resolutions at the start of the year! OK ... Maybe you didn\'t follow them but the important thing is to try! </item>
        <item>Always try to be the best version of yourself! </item>
        <item>Try to compliment the first person you see! Giving a compliment is more fun than receiving it :) </item>
        <item>Take the time to listen to the birds, even in town you can hear them at dawn or at dusk if you listen carefully </item>
        <item>I love you! </item>
        <item>You always have to dream! </item>
        <item>What is your favorite song? I\'m sure you have it in mind now :) </item>
        <item>In spring, the flowers bloom. In summer, the sun shines. In Autumn, the trees are colored. In Winters, pristine snow covers the earth. It\'s just beautiful! </item>
        <item>Think back to the last video on cats (or your favorite animal) that you saw. If you haven\'t seen one then go look at one as soon as possible. If that doesn\'t make you happy then you\'re not human! </item>
        <item>We are not always free in our actions but we are always free in our thoughts! Think of anything you like </item>
        <item>You can always earn more money, but you can never live longer! Cherish every minute of your life </item>
        <item>Stop for a minute, close your eyes and listen to the sounds around you! </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>